<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.video.live.streams"
       name="LiveStreams"
       version="1.1.2"
       provider-name="divingmule">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.beautifulsoup" version="3.0.8"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simple.downloader" version="0.9.1"/>
    <import addon="script.module.simplejson" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>livestreams</summary>
    <description>
      It's up to you ;-) As an alternative to .strm files this add-on lets you add streams by adding items to an xml file.
      Thus giving you a nice list with thumbnails, fanart, and media info if you like.
    </description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.p2p-streams"
       name="p2p-streams"
       version="0.1.1"
       provider-name="enen92 - fightnight">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource"
            library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary>P2P-Streams addon</summary>
    <description lang="en">p2p-Streams addon makes it easy for you to play p2p (peer-to-peer) streams directly in XBMC without the need for external players. Currently supporting Acestream and Sopcast streams it comprises an auto-configuration tool that will download the engines specifically for your platform. At the moment it is available for Linux, Windows and the Raspberry PI (OpenELEC, Raspbmc and Xbian). Other platforms will be supported in the future. Original code for SopCast developed by Cristi - Atlanta; original code for the Acestream Client console provided by NuisMons; Acestream-Engine for the Raspberry Pi based on tarasian666 work; Raspberry PI Sopcast emulator credits go to the amazing community in raspberrypi.org official forum. Fannart and icon by Marquerite. Thanks to them all!</description>
    <description lang="pt">O addon p2p-Streams torna possível assistir de forma simples a streams p2p (peer-to-peer) directamente no XBMC sem necessidade de player externos. De momento suporta streams Ace (Acestreams) e Sopcast e inclui uma ferramenta de autoconfiguração que irá fazer o download da engine correspondente ao seu sistema operativo. De momento, o addon está disponível para Linux, Windows e para todas as distribuições XBMC da Raspberry PI (OpenELEC, Raspbmc, Xbian). Novas plataformas serão adicionadas no futuro. Código original para o Sopcast foi desenvolvido por Cristi - Atlanta; o código original para a consola de cliente Acestream foi desenvolvida por NuisMons; A Acestream-Engine para a Raspberry Pi foi modificada do trabalho original de Tarasian666. Os créditos do emulador Sopcast para a Raspberry Pi vão para a fantástica comunidade do fórum oficial da Raspberry PI (raspberrypi.org). Icon e fannart por Marquerite. Obrigado a Todos!</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
  </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="plugin.video.veetle" version="0.2.3" name="Veetle" provider-name="t0mm0">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="2.1.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.simplejson" version="2.0.10"/>
        <import addon="script.common.plugin.cache" version="1.3.0"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point= "xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <summary>Browse and stream from veetle.com</summary>
        <description>Enables watching streams on veetle.com that are flash enabled.</description>
        <disclaimer>Does not work for 'HD' streams which require a software download.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
    </extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.divingmule.addons" name="divingmule's Unofficial Repository" version="1.0.0">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="divingmule's Unofficial Repository">
		<info compressed="false">http://divingmules-repo.googlecode.com/svn/trunk/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>http://divingmules-repo.googlecode.com/svn/trunk/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="false">http://divingmules-repo.googlecode.com/svn/trunk/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Add-ons that arn't in the official XBMC repository.</summary>
		<description>Add-ons for XBMC, sometimes are a work in progress.</description>
		<disclaimer></disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.p2p-streams.xbmc" name="p2p-streams repository" version="1.0.1" provider-name="enen92 - fightnight">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="p2p-streams Repository">
		<info compressed="false">http://p2p-strm.googlecode.com/svn/addons/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>http://p2p-strm.googlecode.com/svn/addons/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">http://p2p-strm.googlecode.com/svn/addons</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>p2p-streams repository</summary>
   		<description lang="en">Install p2p streams addon for XBMC! p2p-Streams addon makes it easy for you to play p2p (peer-to-peer) streams directly in XBMC without the need for external players. Currently supporting Acestream and Sopcast streams it comprises an auto-configuration tool that will download the engines specifically for your platform. At the moment it is available for Linux, Windows and the Raspberry PI (OpenELEC, Raspbmc and Xbian). Other platforms will be supported in the future. Original code for SopCast developed by Cristi - Atlanta; original code for the Acestream Client console provided by NuisMons; Acestream-Engine for the Raspberry Pi based on tarasian666 work; Raspberry PI Sopcast emulator credits go to the amazing community in raspberrypi.org official forum. Fannart and icon by Marquerite. Thanks to them all!</description>
    		<description lang="pt">Instale o addon p2p-streams para o XBMC! O addon p2p-Streams torna possível assistir de forma simples a streams p2p (peer-to-peer) directamente no XBMC sem necessidade de player externos. De momento suporta streams Ace (Acestreams) e Sopcast e inclui uma ferramenta de autoconfiguração que irá fazer o download da engine correspondente ao seu sistema operativo. De momento, o addon está disponível para Linux, Windows e para todas as distribuições XBMC da Raspberry PI (OpenELEC, Raspbmc, Xbian). Novas plataformas serão adicionadas no futuro. Código original para o Sopcast foi desenvolvido por Cristi - Atlanta; o código original para a consola de cliente Acestream foi desenvolvida por NuisMons; A Acestream-Engine para a Raspberry Pi foi modificada do trabalho original de Tarasian666. Os créditos do emulador Sopcast para a Raspberry Pi vão para a fantástica comunidade do fórum oficial da Raspberry PI (raspberrypi.org). Icon e fannart por Marquerite. Obrigado a Todos!</description>
		<disclaimer></disclaimer>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>

<addon id="repository.t0mm0" name="t0mm0's XBMC Addons" version="1.0.3" provider-name="t0mm0 [dev@onairsoftware.co.uk]">
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="t0mm0's XBMC Addon Repository">
		<info compressed="false">http://github.com/t0mm0/t0mm0-xbmc-plugins/raw/master/addons.xml</info>
		<checksum>http://github.com/t0mm0/t0mm0-xbmc-plugins/raw/master/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
		<datadir zip="true">http://github.com/t0mm0/t0mm0-xbmc-plugins/raw/master/repo/</datadir>
	</extension>
	<extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
		<summary>Install t0mm0's Addons</summary>
		<description>Download and install addons by t0mm0</description>
		<platform>all</platform>
	</extension>
</addon>
</addons>
